ITAI MIZLISH

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT



+97254-2258899



itaim148@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/itai-mizlish/



https://github.com/itaim18



www.itaimiz.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Science in Computer Science

JCT Lev Academic Center

2015 - 2019

CERTIFICATES

The Joy of React

| Josh Comeau

- The complete 2022 Web development Bootcamp.
- · React The Complete Guide.
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Masterclass

| Udemy

SKILLS

- React
- JavaScript & ES6 / ES5
- HTML/ HTML5
- CSS/ CSS3/ SASS and BEM method.
- · Consuming data from APIs.
- · Redux & React Query
- Context-API
- Node.js & express
- MongoDB (mongoose)
- Typescript
- Firebase
- jQuery
- Tailwind & Bootstrap
- · Git, Github. bit.dev

PROFILE

I am a **Frontend Developer** and a Fullstack developer with a strong understanding of Javascript and React.is framework, its cores and hooks. Knowledgeable in DS implementation and algorithms solving in JavaScript and ES6. Experienced in building Frontend and Fullstack architectures from scratch. I'm a Computer Science graduate in the age of 19 and a self learner. A team player who loves to share his aspects on code a problem-solver and thrives on challenges.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

2022 - present

- Design and create architectures for web applications.
- Develop full-stack web apps using MERN structure and firebase.
- · Create more appealing user interfaces using Javascript libraries, CSS technology tools such as modules, tailwind, bootstrap etc.
- Experience in functional programming in JavaScript and knowledgeable in ES6.
- Created a server-client app using a proxy server to help the client consume data from an API using React utilities such as React Router and Redux on the client side and improving app performance with React Query.
- Give talks and lessons on components and Design systems such as Material-UI and Radix primitives in a new aspect.

2016 - 2018 **Tutor**

Israeli Center for Advancement in Math (associated with Bar Ilan University)

- Facilitated annual Science Day activities for children.
- Tutored basic Physics and Aeronautics lessons in schools in the TA Metropolitan Area.
- Graded tests and tutored children with special needs.

Military Service

2019 - 2022

Infantry Unit

Volunteering

2015 - 2018

Krembo Wings

· Assisted and accompanied children with special needs and formed unique connections with them.

LANGUAGES

English

Hebrew

